- Previously on "The Ark"...
- Here we are again.
- Is he even alive?
- [grunting]
- Get him free. Now!
- Easy.
- [gasps]
- Got a visual ahead.
- Guys, I am telling you,
it seemed like Doc was there, right?
And she was the one
who fixed me up.
- I think it's Admiral Hammond.
- Who is she?
- I'm not sure yet.
- Mr. Strickland,
is that your sword?
Did you do this?
- I barely knew
Admiral Hammond,
let alone had a reason
to kill him.
[dramatic music]
[curious music]
[door whooshes]
- So what couldn't wait
till I finished my lunch?
- I've got the rest
of the results of our study.
It's kind of blowing my mind.
The grass is Cynodon dactylon.
- Bermuda grass.
- The trees are poplar,
field maple, and scarlet oak.
- Mm-hmm. And the bird?
- Turdus merula.
- Eurasian blackbird.
They're really common on Earth.
- All of it's common on Earth.
- No kidding.
- But that's crazy.
Why would they all be
on a planet
light-years away from Earth?
- They wouldn't.
You've got it wrong.
Run the data again.
- I've run it three times.
It's accurate.
[device beeping]
[chimes]
- Which means
the same plants and animals
that evolved on Earth
evolved here.
Parallel evolution.
The odds of that are like nil.
- They're not like nil.
They are nil.
- Maybe the people
in those caves know something
that can help us
figure this out.
- The people that knocked
you out and kidnapped you?
Those people?
- Well, now, the idea that
they're humans who evolved here
feels less unlikely.
- They were trying to tell me
and Kelly something.
I'm gonna go see if I can
get back in there,
try to communicate with them.
- Then I'm going with you.
- I think you're both
out of your minds.
But if you insist on going,
I suggest you take
several large men with guns.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Mind if I join you?
- You're not real.
- Yes, I am.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't be.
You're in my head.
- You're the only one
who can perceive me.
You can see me.
You can hear me.
- Okay, okay.
[laughs nervously]
Yes, well, um--so this--
this has got something
to do with that thing
that I took out from behind
my ear back in the caves,
doesn't it?
Somehow that thing--that thing
put you in my head, didn't it?
- See what I mean?
You're so smart.
- So that's a yes, is it?
- I saw an opportunity when
I detected the dormant chip
in your head, so I took it.
- Maddox's frickin'
mind-control chip.
I knew--I knew I should've made
Kabir take it out.
- Good thing she didn't.
- But, no, no.
She said,
don't worry about it, James.
There's no--no risk
involved, James.
Well, this looks like
a big risk to me, Sanji!
- [voice reverberates]
Calm down, buddy.
- Wait a second.
That thing, it was behind
Eva, Garnet's, Kimi's,
and Sanji's ears as well?
But not Ian's, right?
Because Ian, he doesn't have
a chip in his head.
- So smart.
- So what, are you, uh--
you're in all
of their heads as well now,
are you?
- I tried.
But they weren't
attached long enough.
I like you.
You'll be the perfect partner.
- Partner?
Partner for what?
- Oh, it's really quite simple.
Part of me is on Homebase,
but that part is sick.
So it sent a message to part
of me on Ross asking for help.
- Okay.
You sound crazier
than I'm feeling.
- How is that crazy?
On Ross, I fixed you
so you could go back
to Homebase and fix me.
- Why?
- Because by saving me,
you'll save the people
you care about.
- And what does that mean?
- You owe me your life.
I put you back together
good as new.
You should be thanking me.
- Thank you.
Now, please,
get out of my head.
- You might as well
get comfortable with me.
'Cause I'm here to stay.
[uneasy music]
I chose this presentation
because your recent memory
of this woman is... strong.
♪ ♪
So what's the problem?
- The problem?
The prob--Eva!
- Why aren't you resting?
- Um...
I think you need
to take me to med-bay.
- What's wrong?
- There is a woman
in my room, right--
she's not there?
I ca--
- Okay, okay, okay.
Let's get you to Dr. Kabir.
Okay, let's go.
- Nope!
No, I'm fine.
I'm good.
I don't need to go to med-bay.
- Seems like you do.
- No, no, no, no.
I'm fine. I'm all good.
Yeah, just--I think I had
a bit of,
like, a brain fog or something.
But I'm--
I'm totally fine, yeah.
Shouldn't you be on duty?
- I took a break
to check on you.
- Oh, thank you.
That is so nice.
But I'm--I'm fine. I am good.
No, I'm just gonna--
just gonna sleep it off,
I think.
Yeah, I'm just gonna rest up.
So you go.
- Are you sure?
- I am sure.
I promise. Mwah, mwah.
Go. Go, go, go.
Go on, get out of here, you.
[chuckles]
See you in a bit.
All right, bye. Mwah. Bye.
[gasps]
You can frickin' control me?
- [voice reverberates]
Don't try that again.
- Answer me!
- I can't control you
completely.
I can only protect myself.
So far.
- So far?
- And it just occurred to me
why you're so resistant to me.
I mean, you're already paired
with that female.
- Paired with that female.
Yes, yes, yes.
I am already paired
with that female,
thank you very much.
So this, right, whatever
this is, it's not gonna work.
So just get out of my head!
- Now, come to bed.
And get some rest.
You're gonna need
your strength.
- I'll take the chair.
♪ ♪
[uplifting music]
- Dr. Kabir?
I just checked in on James.
I'm worried about him.
- Oh.
Tell me more.
- Well, first he was
talking to the wall.
- Talking to the wall?
- I think.
I mean, it was hard to tell.
Then he couldn't talk at all.
Like, he couldn't
get the words out.
I'm just really worried
about him.
- Okay.
Well, bring him to med-bay.
- I tried.
But he insisted that he's fine.
He said he just has
a little brain fog,
and he needs to rest.
- I mean, he's probably right.
You know,
he's been through hell.
It will take time for him
to get back to normal.
- It felt wrong leaving him
alone, but I'm on duty.
- Okay, what was he doing
when you left him?
- He said he was gonna sleep.
- Good.
That's the best thing for him.
But I'll check in
on him later, okay?
Don't worry.
- Thank you.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- I've gotta tell you,
you almost dying down there,
all I could think about was
how I was gonna lose you
before we even got started.
- Started?
- Yeah, with this.
Us.
- I'm sorry, Ian.
- Oh, no, don't be sorry.
I just wanted to make sure
that you knew
how much I cared about you.
- I do know.
And I care about you too.
But if I'm gonna keep
the respect of the crew,
I have to maintain
professional propriety.
- Oh, come on.
Surely you get to have a life
like everyone else.
[soft music]
- Sometimes I feel like
I'm split into two people.
You know what I mean?
Like, Captain Garnet
and Sharon Garnet.
- Well, if I get a vote,
I vote for Sharon Garnet.
[both chuckle]
♪ ♪
- Ian?
- Yeah?
- We can't let anyone know
about this.
- Know about what?
- This.
♪ ♪
[breathing heavily]
- Captain Garnet
to the bridge.
- You have got
to be kidding me.
- Looks like the universe cast
its vote for Captain Garnet.
- [groans]
- Report.
- We got a garbled
distress beacon.
It's on repeat,
but we can't make
heads or tails of what it says.
- Can you tell if it's GSA?
- It was on
a GSA-encoded frequency.
- Well, can you triangulate
its location?
- Already did.
Looks like there's
no solar system there.
Just empty space, which is odd
but not unheard of.
- All right.
Set a course for the source
of the signal.
Let's see if we can help.
What the hell happened here?
- The distress signal is
coming from the debris.
It was an Ark.
- Oh, God. Which one?
- Can't tell.
I can't find any identifier.
- Captain, we're being dragged
by a very strong gravity force.
- Looks like we dropped
out of FTL
right next to the gravity well.
Not sure of its source,
but it seems
like some form of dark matter.
- Might I suggest
we hightail it out of here
before whatever did this
to the other Ark does it to us?
- Agreed.
Get us out of here, Kimi.
[tense music]
[screeching]
- That doesn't sound good.
- Strong gravity waves
are bending space-time.
It's interfering
with the FTL forming a bubble.
- Kimi, try the NEPS engines.
- The gravity pull
is too strong.
- Damn it!
I can redirect resources
from non-life support systems
to goose the NEPS.
Maybe it'll be enough
to move us further out,
and then, I don't know,
hopefully the FTL will work.
- Do it.
[whirring]
- NEPS overload.
- There has to be
something else we can try.
- I don't think there is.
- Kimi?
- I got nothing.
- We're stranded here.
- Eva, try redirecting power
from the FTL chargers.
And, Kimi, send a K23
distress signal
on the off chance someone is
around who can help us.
[computer chirps]
- Sent.
- Commencing now.
[whirring]
- Look.
The bloody debris disappeared.
How can that be?
- Captain,
the systems are overloaded.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- What the hell happened here?
- The distress signal is
coming from the debris.
It was an Ark.
- Oh, God. Which one?
[birds chirping]
[computer chiming]
- Let's see
if it's still playing
the musical scale password
that worked last time.
[beeping]
[notes playing]
♪ ♪
Huh.
[notes playing]
♪ ♪
- What's that?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- That wasn't there
the last time we were here.
I'd remember it.
Wait!
I don't think
you should touch it.
♪ ♪
- Looks like
the same style lettering
as the slab we dug up.
- This can't be.
[door whirs]
- Mr. Trust!
We found this
at the underground entrance.
- Well, the language
looks the same.
Why didn't anyone see this
the last time
you were out there?
- Alicia says
it wasn't there then.
- So someone put it there
for you to find.
Interesting.
And tell me, the lettering,
has it been the same
the whole time it's been
in your possession?
- Why wouldn't it be?
- Because the symbols
on the slab aren't.
- What?
- Look.
I took these reference photos
when it first came in.
- It changed.
[keypad beeps]
How is that possible?
These words are
chiseled in stone.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[both grunting]
- [groans]
- Who sent you?
[groans]
♪ ♪
- 24, report.
Sending backup.
♪ ♪
[door beeps]
- I'm not dressed.
This better be an emergency.
- It is.
- Oh, it's you.
Come in.
You have something to report?
- Strickland escaped.
- What? How?
- I don't know.
I found Jeffries on the floor,
locked in the cell.
- Idiot!
I should've done it myself.
Is Jeffries even alive?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Tell him
to get his ass out there
with every woman and man
we have and find Felix.
That includes you.
Go. I'll catch up.
♪ ♪
- Alicia.
- Angus, it's so late.
- [gasps] Felix?
- Sorry, I didn't mean
to startle you.
I couldn't be seen
in the corridor knocking,
so I used my code to enter.
I hope you don't mind.
- What's going on?
- They're going to say
I attacked a guard and escaped,
but the truth is,
he was trying to kill me.
- Oh, my God, are you--
- I've got to go into hiding
before they try it again.
- Wait. Who's "they"?
- That's what I need you
to find out.
He was wearing a mask.
My guess is, Ves is behind
all this, but I have no proof.
- Okay, so what do you
want me to do?
- I need you to hack
into the database logs
that Hammond was looking at
regarding Ves.
See what she's hiding.
- But that was all redacted
beyond my clearance.
That encryption codec
is beyond--
- Alicia, I need that
information to clear my name.
- Okay.
If Hammond was careless enough
not to wipe his tracks,
I could probably go back
in the binary code
and find out what password
he entered to get in.
- Never doubted
you could do it.
I'll be hiding out
in the forest.
- Wait.
[device beeping]
I've turned off the tracking
and set an encrypted channel
I can reach you on.
- Thank you.
If you find anything,
take it to Zed Avega.
I've come to trust him.
But don't trust anyone else.
We don't know
who's working with Ves.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[tense music]
- What the hell happened here?
- The distress signal is
coming from the debris.
It was an Ark.
- Okay.
And what else do you think
we should try?
But there has to be a way.
- There's two of you now?
- 219.
- Huh?
- There are
219 instances of me.
[unsettling music]
♪ ♪
- Okay.
[clears throat]
What the hell is going on?
- All right.
I've told you this 219 times,
but I'll try it again.
We're trapped in a closed
causal temporal recursion.
- A what now?
- A time loop.
- Oh, right.
A time loop. Okay.
- It's being caused
by the warping of space-time
by a gravity well
holding us here.
- Not buying it.
- Of course not. You never do.
- Yeah, because you're on
a chip in my head, right?
So you see what I see.
So how would you know about
this supposed time loop,
but I don't?
- Because I'm not
flesh and blood.
I'm software in a quantum chip.
I don't perceive time
as you do.
- Mm. Bullshit.
- Look, they've done this
219 times.
I keep trying,
but I can't figure out
how to get us out of it.
- Uh-huh.
- You have to trust me
if we're going to have
a chance.
Otherwise, we blow up
over and over again.
- And why do you care?
Seriously, why do you care
if we get out of this or not?
- You're still not getting it.
You and I have to get to
Homebase as soon as possible.
To do that, we have to get
out of this loop.
And to do that,
I really need your cooperation.
- [breathes deeply]
Okay.
I'll bite.
What is it that you would
want me to do?
- Okay.
In past instances,
I've been able to convince you
to look at engineering,
sub-engineering,
and electrical.
But no matter what I try,
I can't get you
to go to the bridge.
- Yeah, you're damn straight.
Because I can't trust you
not to try and make me
do something
that's gonna endanger
this entire ship and its crew.
- Which is what you tell me
every time.
But I need to go to the bridge
to see exactly what happens.
- No, not a chance.
- And in every instance,
I can't understand
why you won't go and save Eva.
She's critically injured
on the bridge.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Oh! Sorry.
Dr. Kabir.
- Yeah.
- Uh, listen, is, uh--
is Eva okay?
- Oh.
Far as I know, she's fine.
But how about you?
Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
No, I'm, uh--I'm fine.
♪ ♪
- I can redirect resources
from non-life support systems
to goose the NEPS.
Maybe that'll be enough
to move us further out.
And then hopefully
the FTL will work.
- Do it.
- Oh, look. You lied.
- [shushing]
I need to watch.
[whirring]
- NEPS overload.
- There has to be
something else we can try.
- I don't think there is.
- Uh, Kimi?
- I got nothing. I'm sorry.
- Well, I think
we're stranded here.
- Eva, try redirecting power
from the FTL chargers.
And, Kimi, send a K23
distress signal
on the off chance someone
is around who can help us.
[computer chirps]
- Sent.
- Commencing now.
- Look.
The bloody debris disappeared.
How can that be?
[computer chirps]
- Captain, the systems
are overloaded.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- But there has to be a way.
- Wait, there's two of you now?
- 220.
- Huh?
- There are
220 instances of me.
- The guard was
bringing Strickland dinner.
Felix jumped him
and broke his arm.
- Do we have any idea why?
- What do you mean?
Felix Strickland murdered
Hammond in cold blood
and wanted to escape without
facing the consequences.
- That doesn't sound like the
Strickland I've come to know.
- You know a different man
than I do.
As far as I'm concerned,
his escape proves his guilt.
We need to hunt him down.
Alive or dead, if necessary.
- Slow down, Ves.
We don't even have a motive
for why Felix would
kill Hammond.
I want to talk to the guard.
- You do that.
I'm sure he'll tell you
the same thing he told me.
- [sighs]
- Mr. Avega.
I have some information.
And Felix Strickland said
you're the only one
I should trust it with.
- Okay.
- I hacked
into the GSA database
to find out
what Hammond was investigating.
That's what I found.
- Ves was a commander
of a Black Thorn unit.
- Yes.
The deepest secret black ops
division of the GSA.
I never believed
it even existed.
- Oh, it exists.
I've had firsthand experience
with that nasty little group.
I killed three of them myself
when they were sent
to assassinate me
back on Earth.
- They tried
to assassinate you?
- I was a very high-ranking
EF commander.
- I wonder if that means
the EF hunters
are also part of Black Thorn.
- Why would that be relevant?
- Because we have one
in our jail.
[tense music]
- I can't confirm or deny
the existence of Black Thorn.
- [chuckles]
I know you were an EF hunter.
You've admitted that.
- Let me guess.
Given the two of you were EF,
you don't like me very much?
- Not at all, in fact.
- Oh.
What you gonna do, kill me?
- Hmm.
[breathes deeply]
[chuckles]
Let's try this.
Hypothetically,
if Black Thorn existed,
would EF hunters be part
of that organization?
- I can't confirm or deny
the existence of Black Thorn.
- Wasting my time.
- People who know too much
can get killed in this jail.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- But if I were able
to get you released,
I'm guessing
suddenly you'd know a lot.
[knock at door]
It's open.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes.
You're the only other person
who knows about the situation.
And the irony is,
I can't consult
either one of my
co-council members,
Strickland or Ves.
- What did Lati say?
- Not much.
She wants to be released
before she'll talk.
- Are you gonna let her go?
- I don't know.
It's a bit like deciding
between drinking arsenic
and drinking strychnine.
Either one will kill you.
- I guess it depends
on who's arsenic
and who's strychnine
in this metaphor.
- What do you mean?
- To me, Ves is arsenic.
You know, it's tasteless,
it's odorless,
and very difficult
to detect in an autopsy.
She could get away
with killing the admiral,
but you may never know
what else she's hiding
if you don't make a deal
with Lati.
- Uh-huh.
- Strychnine is violent
and obvious, like Lati.
- [chuckles]
- I really tortured
that metaphor, didn't I?
- Oh, yes, you did.
- Sorry.
- But in your unique way,
Alicia, you made a valid point.
Lati is an open book,
and we know exactly
what she's done.
- Or attempted to do.
She didn't actually succeed
in killing Eva or me.
- But she was an EF hunter.
Who knows how many of my
friends and colleagues
she killed.
EF hunters were the worst
of the worst in my world.
They killed many of my friends.
- That may be true,
but we were at war.
I mean, the EF killed
a lot of my friends.
Should I hate you for every
GSA person you killed?
- Huh.
Alicia, you're very wise
for such a young age.
- Thank you.
- What are you doing?
- Lati didn't kill any EF.
- How do you know that?
- Oh, I hacked the admiral's
password, remember?
I used it to remove all
the redactions on her record.
Lati was on "Ark 15"
her whole tour of duty.
There were no EF onboard.
- Still, she was and is
an attempted murderer.
- I wonder
what Ves is trying to hide
so badly that she would
murder the admiral
and frame Felix for it.
- I can only imagine.
- So are you gonna make a deal
with Lati and find out?
- I can't find
any sort of mechanism
to change this lettering.
It's seemingly chiseled
indelibly into the damn stone.
- Do you think
the triangle we brought back
is made of the same material?
- I don't know.
Bring it over here.
- Oh.
- Fascinating.
[suspenseful music]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
- Wait.
- [yelps]
Boy, I'm on 22 hours
in this lab with no sleep.
You nearly gave me
a heart attack.
- Sorry.
Do you think it's a good idea
to put that in the hole?
Like, it could explode
or something.
- There's only one way
to find out.
- [exclaims]
Wow.
- [sighs]
Well, that was anticlimactic.
- I thought it was cool.
- Wait, this thing has
started emitting sound waves
outside of our hearing range.
- It wasn't doing that
before, right?
- Nope.
Let me try and use
Alicia's technique
to drop the frequency.
Right, can you hear anything?
- No.
- That should've worked.
So the sounds can be detected
by our instrumentation,
but they can't be adjusted
so that we can hear them.
- [groans]
Uh...
so electronics can detect it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Kelly could hear sounds
in the underground
that I couldn't hear when
she had her implants turned on.
Maybe she'll be able
to hear it.
- So what are you waiting for?
Bring her over here.
- I'll bring her over here.
♪ ♪
- [scoffs]
You asked to see me?
- Yeah.
Just thought you should know,
Avega wants me
to roll over on you.
- I'm not sure
what you're talking about.
- Don't worry.
I kept my mouth shut.
Once a Thorn, always a Thorn.
- That's adorable.
Just have no idea
what that means.
- Good.
Then I guess I can tell them
whatever they want to know.
- And what exactly
do they want to know?
- They think you killed
that admiral.
- I don't know
what you're talking about.
- They also think
that you framed Strickland
and then sent someone
to kill him in jail.
- Well, they have
quite the imagination.
- You know I was here, right?
When that Thorn came in
to kill Strickland?
And I can ID the guy.
- What does that
have to do with me?
- Well, he kind of said
a few things
that incriminate you.
- And I assume
you want something.
- Only my freedom.
- [chuckles]
Well, that's impossible.
You're an attempted murderer.
- And you're a successful one.
- If that were true,
why wouldn't I just kill you?
[ominous music]
- Go for it.
- It's like you want me to.
- No.
I actually don't believe
you would kill a fellow Thorn.
- You see,
that's where you're wrong.
If I could kill an admiral,
why would I hesitate
for one second
to kill a nobody like you?
- And I thought we had
that Black Thorn
sisterhood thing going.
- Step aside, Zed.
[grunts, gasps]
- You forgot I have
the same training you do.
- You don't have
the authority to do this.
- Oh, I think I do.
- Just so you know, I didn't
see or hear the attacker,
much less know
if he was Black Thorn.
- I won't forget this.
- Neither will I.
[door slams]
It was kind of fun.
[suspenseful music]
- Don't worry, Ves.
You'll get a fair trial.
♪ ♪
[beeping]
- All right, I've told you this
about 230 times,
but I'll try again.
We're trapped in a time loop.
- Ooh. Time loop.
I'm not buying it.
- Of course not.
All right,
I'm just gonna jump ahead.
Eva is critically injured
on the bridge.
- What?
- Dr. Kabir is about
to come around the corner.
- What?
- Oh!
both: Sorry.
Dr. Kabir, listen, is Eva okay?
both: As far as I know,
she's fine.
But how about you?
Are you okay?
both: Yeah, I'm fine.
- How did you know
what we were gonna say?
- I keep telling you,
we're in a time loop.
I've heard it
hundreds of times.
- Do it.
- You lied.
- Shh.
I need to watch.
- NEPS overload.
- There has to be
something else we can try.
- I don't think there is.
- Kimi?
- I got nothing.
I'm sorry.
- Great.
I think we're stranded.
- Eva, try redirecting power
from the FTL chargers.
- Stop her
from redirecting power.
It will blow us up.
- Kimi, send a K23
distress signal
on the off chance someone
is around who can help us.
- Eva, don't.
Don't, don't, don't.
- Brice!
- Brice, what are you doing?
- I'm sorry, mate.
- Have you lost your mind?
- Yeah. Maybe. I think so.
- K23 sent.
- Uh, guys,
the core's overloading.
- What?
- Look.
The debris has disappeared.
[tense music]
- What the hell happened here?
- The distress signal is
coming from the debris.
It was an Ark.
- Oh, God.
- Watch out.
- Huh?
Oh!
- Oh! Sorry.
- Dr. Kabir.
both: Listen, is Eva okay?
both: As far as I know,
she's fine.
But how are you doing?
Are you okay?
both: Yeah, I'm fine.
- How'd you know
what we were gonna say?
- I keep telling you,
we are in a time loop.
- Oh, God, which one?
- Can't tell.
I can't find any identifier.
- Captain, we're being dragged
by a very strong gravity force.
- We dropped out of FTL
right next to the gravity well.
Not sure of its source,
but it seems like
some form of dark matter.
- Might I suggest
we hightail it out of here
before whatever did this
to that Ark does it to us?
- Agreed.
Get us out of here, Kimi.
Set a course for Homebase.
- Did we ever try to stop
Kimi from doing that?
[screeching]
- That doesn't sound good.
- Yeah, you stopped her.
Didn't help.
- Strong gravity waves
are bending space-time.
It's interfering with the FTL
forming a bubble.
- Kimi, try the NEPS engines.
- What about trying
to stop that?
- Yeah.
- Brice, who are you
talking to?
- Just--
- The gravity pull
is too strong.
- Damn it. I can redirect
non-life support systems
to goose the NEPS.
Maybe it'll be enough
to move us out far.
- Do it.
- Have we tried stopping that?
- We've tried stopping
everything they do.
[computer chirps]
- Overload.
- There has to be
something else we can try.
- There's gotta be something
that we haven't tried.
- I don't think there is.
- We've tried everything.
- Kimi?
- I got nothing. I'm sorry.
- I think we're stranded here.
- Eva, try redirecting power
from the FTL chargers.
- Yeah, stopped that too.
- Kimi, send a K23
distress signal
on the off chance someone
is around who can help us.
- Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
We answered that distress call.
- Yes.
- So maybe
we can prevent ourselves
ever coming here
in the first place.
- Yes!
- Kimi, belay that order.
Don't send that signal.
- Whoa! Why, Brice?
- Because that debris
out there, that's us.
♪ ♪
- What?
- Should I send?
- Look.
The bloody debris disappeared.
- Don't send, Kimi.
- Starting the NEPS now.
[computer beeps, NEPS whirs]
♪ ♪
Captain,
the NEPS is overloaded.
- Can't let anyone know
about this.
- Know about what?
- This.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- You know, I just had
the weirdest déjà vu.
- [laughs]
Shut up.
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Hey, what's up?
- That took you long enough.
♪ ♪
- Report.
- Still on course.
- All systems are normal.
- Maintain course for Homebase.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Did you just do something
to me?
- No. Why?
- Because I feel like
I've been doing
laps around the ship
or something.
- Then lay down, get some rest.
- You did, didn't you?
You did something to me.
- Told you, I can't
control you like that.
- Then why am I so tired?
- Don't know.
Easy solution?
Go to sleep.
- And what are you gonna do?
- What do you want me to do?
- Honestly?
I want you to leave me alone.
[grunts]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- What do you want
the team to do now?
- You should just hold
their heels for now.
I'll make a move
when the time is right.
- I don't hear anything.
- Would you mind
turning on your implants?
[device beeps]
[electric pulsing]
[screeching]
- [screaming]
Turn if off!
[screams]
- I can't turn it off.
- I'm gonna move the slab
away from her.
[yells]
Ah!
- Angus!
- I'm okay.
[grunts]
I'm okay.
- [screaming]
[screeching stops]
[panting]
- Kelly?
Are--are you all right?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Guys.
Guys, you have to see this.
- Hey, come on.
- [grunts]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- It's in English.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪